Hey, you guys. Hey, what are you doing?
嗨，大家！在幹什麼?
-Figuring out our wedding plans. -Funny. We were doing the same thing.
-籌備婚禮 -有趣得很, 我們也正合計這事呢
It's really crazy. The hall, the dress, the food.
瘋了, 場地, 服裝, 食品
-I had no idea how expensive this was. -Yeah, it is really pricey.
-沒想到結個婚這麼貴 -是很貴
-I freaked when I heard the numbers. -So, what did you two do about it?
-第一次算出結婚費用，我被那個數字嚇呆了 -結果你們怎麼做的?
It was simple. I came up with some cost-cutting solutions..
簡單, 我各個項目都想出了一些省錢的方案
wrote out a list, and Monica told me to go to hell.
結果莫妮卡叫我去死
There's no way around it. Just accept that this is gonna cost a lot of money.
沒錢好省的, 接受事實, 這的確所費不貲
I heard that weddings are, like, a $40 billion-a-year industry.
聽說每年花在結婚上的錢高達400億
Yeah. And I'm responsible for just, like, half of that.
這其中我貢獻過半
I don't know. It's a lot of money to spend on one day.
我不知道, 一天花這麼多錢
Hey, I've been married before, I don't need a big wedding.
嘿, 我以前結過婚 我都沒有盛大的婚禮
All I ask is that you don't do ecstasy and make out with my brother.
我所想知道的是你沒有迷上我弟弟並和他上床
But really, it does seem like this money could be put to better use.
我覺得這錢應該用在更有意義的事上
Hey, you could buy a ton of Amway products.
嘿, 你可以買一噸安利的產品
-Or give it all to charity. -Oh, that's great.
-或者全部捐給慈善機構 -喔, 這個想法不錯
How am I gonna unload all those Amway products?
那些安利的東西該怎麼樣卸貨呢?
Are you serious?
當真?
Yeah. How would you feel if we gave all the wedding money to charity..
把婚禮經費捐獻給慈善事業
and we just got married at City Hall?
我們就到市政廳登個記？
I think it would make me wanna marry you even more.
這讓我越發想娶你了!
I gotta say, you guys, that's an incredible gesture.
高姿態! 很好
Maybe you do that next time you get married.
下次你結婚也這麼干如何?
No, no, no. The next time's gonna be Hawaii at sunset.
下次我要在夏威夷斜陽下結婚
But maybe the time after that.
下下次吧
The One With The Home Study
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-Hey. What's going on? -Hey.
-嘿！ 忙啥呢？ -嘿！
Our adoption social worker is coming, so we're cleaning the apartment.
領養中心有人來家訪，所以我們在掃除
"We"?
我們？
You know you don't want me to help. You can't have it both ways.
你不想我摻和，拖你後腿！
Is this the person who decides whether or not you get a baby?
這個人說了算？
-She's coming to see where we live. -And it has to go perfectly.
－差不多，這人來視察我們的生活環境 －我們必須表現得完美
If she doesn't like us, she can keep us off every adoption list in the state.
若她有絲毫不滿，我們就永遠沒戲
Hey, maybe I should stop by. She could be a soap opera fan.
我可以過來友情協力一把 她沒準愛看肥皂劇
It's very impressive when the little people know a celebrity.
小人物認識演藝名流，可以蓬壁生輝呢
"Little people"?
小人物？
"Celebrity."
名流
So I think I'm just about done here.
差不多滿分了
Unless you have any bad stuff hidden somewhere, like porn or cigarettes?
除非你還有什麼，像色情書刊，香煙？
What?
什麼？
-No. -Chandler.
－才沒有！ －錢德
I don't, and I'm offended by the insinuation.
你無中生有，污人清白
So there's not a magazine under the couch..
沙發下沒有雜誌？
or cigarettes taped to the back of the toilet tank..
廁所水箱後沒有一包香煙？
or a filthy video in the VCR?
錄像機裡沒有A片?
I'll admit to the cigarettes and magazine. But that tape is not mine.
香煙和雜誌我認帳，但錄像帶
不是我的！
-It isn't mine. -I guess we'll never know whose it is.
-也不是我的！ -永遠不會知道是誰的了！
May I help you?
可以幫忙嗎？
Yes. We're here to make a rather sizable donation to the children.
我們來捐錢給孩子
Any contribution, large or small, is appreciated.
捐錢不論多少，心意都是一樣重 我們都會感激
I think you're gonna appreciate the crap out of this one.
數目這樣大，你一定會異常感激
-Well, this is very generous. -And we don't want any recognition.
-你們真大方 -我們不留名．
This is completely anonymous.
匿名捐助
Completely anonymous. From two kind strangers.
完全匿名 兩個好人
Mr. X and Phoebe Buffay.
X先生和菲比布費
We can put your names in our newsletter.
我們可以把二位的名字登到新聞通訊裡
-Not necessary. -Buffay is spelled B-U-F-F-A-Y.
－沒必要 －布費的拼法是：Buffay
And X is spelled "Mike Hannigan."
X先生的寫法是：麥克.哈納根
Possible headline: Attractive Couple Makes World Better.
也許標題應該寫: 迷人的夫婦讓世界變的更好
Well, on behalf of the children, thank you both very much.
我代表孩子們多謝兩位
-I'm glad we did this. It feels so good. -It does. It feels really good.
-感覺真棒 -是啊，非常棒。
Oh, look. And we get these free T-shirts.
還有免費T恤拿
Actually, that's the shirt I wore to the gym.
那是我健身穿的
It's moist.
難怪是濕的
-Hi. Emma will be up in a minute. -Oh, good.
-艾瑪會很快起床的 -哦，天啊。
Hey, Ross, listen. I heard about you and Charlie. I'm really sorry.
嘿，羅斯 聽說你跟查莉的事了, 替你難過
That's okay. I'm sure there are tons of other beautiful paleontologists out there.
沒事, 美貌的考古學家多的是!
-Absolutely. -There was one. She's it.
-當然! -只有一個!就是她!
All the rest look like they should live under a bridge.
其他的就好像是橋洞居民一樣!
So, what are you gonna do today?
今天想怎麼玩?
I was thinking of taking Emma to the playground.
帶艾瑪去街心遊樂場怎麼樣?
Oh, my God. What?
什麼?
Like I said, I was thinking of taking Emma to the Museum of Knives and Fire.
我又沒說帶她去武器彈藥博物館
Okay, look, Ross. I do not want Emma going to the playground.
我反對艾瑪去遊樂場
Because..?
因為?
All right, if you must know, I had a traumatic..
好吧，如果你想知道…
swing incident when I was little.
我小時候蕩鞦韆遇險
-Seriously? -Yes. I was 4 years old.
-真的? -我才四歲
And I was on the swing..
我蕩鞦韆
and then all of a sudden my hair got tangled in the chain.
突然頭髮纏到鐵鏈
And to get me out, my mom had to cut a big chunk of my hair.
結果老媽剪掉我一大縷頭髮, 才救我出來
And it was uneven for weeks.
結果有好幾星期頭髮都不整齊
And you made it through that?
你竟熬了過來?
I wonder who's gonna play you in the movie.
簡直可以拍成電影
Okay, fine, you can make fun of me. I do not want Emma going there.
你儘管拿我取笑, 反正我就是不想艾瑪去
And I was thinking Claire Danes.
而且我在想克萊爾·丹妮絲
Look, I'm sorry to hear about your tragedy.
你的悲劇令我同情
But the swings are perfectly safe. And besides, Emma loves them.
不過鞦韆很安全 而且艾瑪喜歡蕩鞦韆
-You should come, and you'll see. -Those things go, like,40 miles an hour.
-我們同去, 你就知道了 -鞦韆速度40英里/小時
And there's that moment when you're at the top..
蕩到高處
when you just don't know if you're gonna return back to Earth.
鬼才知道會不會返回地球
Space is filled with orbiting children.
宇宙充滿小孩子繞軌道運行
Look, please, just come on.
來嘛
When you see the look on Emma's face, I swear, you won't regret it.
你若看見艾瑪的表情, 決不會後悔
-All right. -Good.
-好吧 -太好了。
You don't wanna be a mom who passes her irrational fears to her children.
你不會像有的媽媽那樣 把自己愚昧的恐懼遺傳給小孩吧
"Irrational, " huh?
愚昧?
I'll remember that next time you freak out about a spider in your apartment.
下次你被家裡的蜘蛛嚇到 我們再談這個話題
That's the same. I'm sure there are 30 different species of poisonous swings.
這兩個可以相提並論嗎! 鞦韆上有30種毒液?
Oh, my God. The adoption lady is early.
哦，天，領養中心的來早了
Okay. Okay. Here we go. Here we go.
好的好的.鎮靜鎮靜!!!
Stand up straight.
站直咯
Big smile.
微笑
Hello. Is this the Creepy residence?
你好, 請問這是"毛骨悚然"家嗎?
We're waiting for the adoption lady. But I'm glad you're here.
還以為是領養中心的來了 你來得正好
I was cleaning this morning and I found this.
今早打掃時發現的, 不知道你用不用得上
I don't know if you wanna use it, but..
我不知道你是不是想用, 但是.........
Oh, this is so sweet of you.
你真好
But I won't be needing a veil. I actually won't be wearing a dress at all.
不過我不需要頭紗, 我根本不需要服裝
I told you, I am not coming to a naked wedding!
裸體婚禮, 我不會參加的!
No. We're not having a big reception.
我們不會開招待會
We took the wedding money and donated it to a children's charity.
我們把婚禮經費捐給兒童慈善事業了
That's crazy!
你瘋啦?
-Generous. -Crazy generous.
-慷慨啊！ -你瘋啦?
I'm sorry. I can't imagine giving up my one wedding day like that.
抱歉, 只是無法想像. 一生只有一次啊
Well, we're different. I don't care about having a huge party.
我們不一樣! 我不在乎什麼盛大婚禮
This is really nice for you, but..
頭紗是很美, 但是
Oh, please. I put this on and I just look like..
你看我戴上, 簡直就--
Well, radiant.
美極
All right, but who cares? I don't need a pretty veil and a fancy dress.
管它!我不需要頭紗婚紗這些玩意
That's right. You're making a commitment.
對! 你們是互許終身
You know, that's the same whether you do it at the Plaza or..
不管在廣場舉行還是別的什麼地方都是一樣
-Where you gonna do it? -City Hall.
-你選了啥地方? -市政廳
Oh, that sounds nice.
好地方
I was just there for jury duty. They've really spruced that place up.
市政廳的人該忙不過來了
Okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. I've made my decision.
沒關係, 這是我自己的決定
What I really want is a great big wedding.
但我真正想要的, 只是一個盛大的婚禮
-But you gave all the money to charity. -Well, I'll just ask for it back.
-但錢已經捐啦 -可以要回來
-I don't think you can do that. -Why not?
-不行吧 -怎麼不行?
This is her wedding day. That's way more important than some stupid kids.
她結婚!這可比什麼 愚蠢的小孩子重要多了!
That's sweet, honey, but save something for the adoption lady.
說得好, 省著點, 等領養中心的人來了 再表演不好嗎
-All right, okay. Be careful. -Okay.
-好，準備就緒 -好
Careful. Watch her hair. Watch her hair!
小心, 小心她頭髮
-Rach, she's got, like, three hairs. -I know. I know.
-她才三根毛! -我知道，我知道
But they're just so beautiful. Oh, my God, I just pulled one out.
但是很漂亮 糟糕, 扯掉一根
I promise you she's safe. Watch how much she loves this.
我保證，她很安全, 你看她多喜歡玩鞦韆
-Okay. Okay. -Are you ready, sweetie? Here we go.
-好吧好吧 -你準備好了嗎, 親愛的? 開始嘍
Okay, careful. Okay.
小心
She's smiling.
她笑了
Look at that, she does like it.
她真的很喜歡
See, I told you.
看, 我告訴過你的吧
Oh, my God. Look at her, she's a little daredevil.
哦, 天啊, 看看她, 真有不怕死的精神.
-Oh, God. Let me push. Can I push? -Oh, absolutely.
-讓我推好不好? -哦，當然。
Oh, God. Okay, get the camera. It's in the diaper bag.
你拿相機, 在尿布包裡
Okay.
好。
See? Scared of the swings. I bet you feel pretty silly.
還怕鞦韆, 真夠傻吧?
-We're asking for the money back? -It's for our wedding day.
-我們真要把錢要回來? -結婚要用!
Now, is this guy gay or straight? Because one of us has to start flirting.
這小子喜歡男的女的? 我們非得出美人計
You here to make another donation the same day?
同一天捐兩次錢
I don't think that's ever happened before.
前所未有呢
Gay. Go.
是個同性戀, 你上
Oh, my God, I love your shirt.
你衣裳真帥
The donation we made earlier? Well, we want it back.
今天捐的錢, 我們想要回
Excuse me?
啊?
Okay, that money was for a big wedding we thought we didn't want.
那是辦婚禮的錢, 我們本想從簡
But it turns out we do.
但現在我們改變了主意
So you're asking us to refund your donation to the children?
要我們退還你們捐給孩子們的錢?
Yeah.
對!
This feels really good.
聽來不錯
I'm sorry. I am. But this wedding's just really important to me.
對不起, 但婚禮對我相當重要
Hey, it's none of my business. Besides, this is probably a good thing.
關我啥事 這也許是好事
We've really been spoiling the children, what with all the food and warm clothing.
別把孩子慣壞了 讓他們吃飽穿暖怎麼行
That's not fair. A person's wedding is important.
這麼說不公平, 結婚是大事
And especially to me.
尤其對我!
I didn't have a graduation party. And I didn't go to prom.
我沒參加過畢業典禮, 沒有畢業舞會
And I spent my sweet 16 being chased around a tire yard..
在我的甜蜜16歲,
by an escaped mental patient who, in his own words, wanted to:
我被精神病人狂追 他還說
"Kill me, or whatever."
"殺了我什麼的"
So I deserve a real celebration.
我應當有個隆重的婚禮!
And I'm not gonna let some sweaty little man make me feel badly about it.
你個流汗男, 別想讓我內疚!
She could've been talking about either one of us.
她可能在說我們中的一個
Okay. Here we go.
好的, 來吧
Good luck.
祝好運
Tongue, really?
舌吻?
Hi, I'm Laura. I'm here for your adoption interview.
我叫勞拉, 我來做領養家訪
Hi, I'm Monica. And this is Chandler.
我叫莫妮卡, 這是錢德
-Please come in. -Thank you.
-請進！ -謝謝
-Would you like something to drink? -Water would be fine.
-請進.喝點什麼? -喝水可以了
We're so glad that you're here.
很高興你終於來了
We're excited about getting this process started.
我們好興奮，要開始領養小孩了
Because we love kids. Love them to death.
我們愛小孩, 愛得要死
Well, not actually to death. That's just a figure of speech.
不是要孩子"死", 只是修辭手法
We love kids the appropriate amount..
我們愛孩子, 不多不少
as allowed by law.
符合法律法規
-Your place is just lovely. -Thank you.
-你們家好可愛 -謝謝
Yes, this building does have a wholesome, family feel to it.
這棟樓有很多家住戶
I feel like I've been here before. Any other couples in the building adopting?
我好像來過, 這裡還有誰申請領養?
Is that that couple on the first floor? We should get a baby before them.
一樓那家? 我們應該比他們先要孩子
That guy tried to sell me drugs.
他還想賣毒品給我
But other than that, wholesome, wholesome building.
其他都是好人
-What? -I realized why I remember this place.
-怎麼？ -我想起來了, 難怪來過
-Really? What is it? -Oh, it's nothing.
-怎麼? -哦，沒什麼！
I went on a date with a guy who lived in this building. It didn't end very well.
我和一個男人約會, 結果無疾而終
That wouldn't, by any chance, be Joey Tribbiani?
那人該不是叫喬伊崔比阿尼吧?
-Yes! -Of course it was.
-就是他! -當然是他
We had a great night. In the morning, he promised he'd call and he didn't.
良宵過後, 他說他再打電話給我 結果再沒聯絡!
Rat bastard!
這混球!
-So you're not friends with him? -Oh, God, no.
-你們該不是他朋友? -當然不是!不!
-No, no, no. -No. Nope.
-當然不是!不! -當然不是！
Well, I'm sorry I brought it up.
抱歉提這事
So are either one of you planning on staying at home?
那麼你們當中有人打算待在家裡嗎？
Hello? Anybody in there order a celebrity?
有人嗎? 名人駕到
What was that?
什麼人?
That's just some crazy guy who roams the halls here.
過道上的瘋子
He's great with kids, though.
不過他對小孩很慈祥
-Ross. Oh, my God, are you okay? -Son of a bitch!
-羅斯，噢，天啊， 你還好? -他娘的!
Oh, relax. I didn't say the F-word.
別緊張，我又沒說F打頭那個字!
Ross, see, I told you! Those swings are evil!
羅斯，看, 早告訴你了, 鞦韆危險
That's the last time Emma is getting on one of those things for her entire life.
算了, 這輩子再也不許艾瑪接近它
No, no, no. Okay, it wasn't the swing's fault. It was my fault.
別這樣, 不是鞦韆的錯, 是我錯
And kind of that kid's fault.
還有他的錯
Who is still laughing. Nice.
他還笑, 算你恨
Come on. Can we just get out of here before somebody else gets hurt?
在再有人受傷之前，我們走吧
No. Wait. I have an idea. I want you to get on the swing..
這樣吧, 你去蕩鞦韆, 你就會…
and you'll see that there's nothing to be afraid of.
發現那有多安全
I know what this is all about.
我明白了
You've always been jealous of my hair.
你一貫嫉妒我頭髮
I just think you're an adult, okay? And you should get over your silly fears.
這才是成年人的做法 克服愚蠢的恐懼
-All right, fine. I'll do it. -Good.
-好!誰怕誰 -好！
-If you hold a spider. -Where?! Where?!
-如果你敢抓蜘蛛 -在哪兒?
If you hold a spider.
我說"如果"你敢抓蜘蛛
I know.
聽見了
Guys, is everything okay? It's me, Joey.
沒事吧? 是我, 喬伊--
Adoption!
領養!
What's going on?
到底什麼事?
Oh, it's just like I said, that crazy..
就是那個瘋子...
Bert, roaming the halls.
叫bert的 在過道上跑
-Guys? -Keep on roaming, Bert!
-嗨！ -bert, 接著跑
We don't want any crazy today!
今天我們不看你瘋了
Is he all right out there by himself?
他獨自一個在外面，不會出事吧?
Oh, yeah. He has a caretaker. His older brother..
沒事, 他哥照顧他
Ernie.
叫ernie
-Bert and Ernie? -You can't make this stuff up.
-Bert 和 Ernie? (芝麻街的動畫角色)? -無巧不成書
-What's going on? -We'll talk later! Everything's fine!
-怎麼了？ -我們等會再說，一切都好！
Everything doesn't sound fine.
聽起來一切都不好！
Bert and Ernie have a big yellow bird.
Bert 和 Ernie 有一隻大黃鳥！
You never told me about that guy and your sweet 16.
你沒說過你16歲時被男人追殺的故事
-I'm sorry about that. -Oh, it ended okay.
-真可憐 -結局還算好
One of my friends shot him.
我朋友斃了他
At least you'll get a proper wedding. You really deserve that.
至少你會有個體面婚禮, 你該得的
Yeah, I really do. You know, I had nothing growing up.
沒錯, 我這輩子還沒風光過
Just like the kids I took the money from.
就像被我剝奪金錢的那些孩子一樣
No. No, no. I see where this is going. Don't make me go back there.
看出你苗頭了, 別又想讓我退回去
I'm sorry, but I want to regive the money to the children.
抱歉, 但我又想把錢給孩子們了
But we can't. I mean, you called that guy a sweaty little man.
但是我們不能, 我是說 你管那男人叫流汗男
Unless you were talking about me. We never really cleared that up.
除非你在說我 我們從沒真正弄乾淨過
Look, I can't have a wedding with this money now. It's tainted.
我不能用這錢辦婚事, 這不道德
Fine, we'll give the money back.
好吧, 退回去作數
If that guy at the charity gives us a hard time..
如果慈善捐助處那傢伙又叫咱們難看
my friend hasn't shot anyone in a really long time.
我朋友的老槍好久沒見過血了
I must say this seems like a lovely environment to raise a child in.
我想說, 這個家庭培養小孩似乎很理想
You are welcome to look under any of the furniture..
你盡可以在各種傢俱下面搜查
because, believe me, you won't find any porn or cigarettes under there.
絕無色情書刊和香煙什麼的!
Before we look around, let me make sure I have everything I need up to here.
在到處看看之前, 要問你們一些問題
Why don't I show you the baby's room.
帶你看看嬰兒房
-What are you doing? -You wouldn't let me in.
-你幹啥? -你不讓我進來
-I thought you were in trouble. -Well, we're not.
-我以為你們出事了 -才沒有!
But you called me "Bert."
但你叫我"bert",
That's our code word for danger.
那是"危險"的暗號
-We don't have a code word. -We don't?
-我們沒約定過什麼暗號 -是嗎？
We really should.
應該約一個
From now on, "Bert" will be our code word for danger.
從今往後，"bert"就用來作為 遇到危險的暗號
So that was the baby's room.
參觀完嬰兒房
-What room should we see next? -Any room that isn't behind this couch.
-下面參觀哪裡？ -除了沙發下面都可以參觀！
Some people don't get him, but I think he's really funny.
有些人不懂他的笑話 但我覺得他真幽默
I did not care for that.
我不在乎被你粗暴對待
You have to leave.
你得迴避
You slept with our social worker and never called her back.
你和這個社工睡過，再沒聯絡她
She is still pissed, so she can't see you.
她還在生你的氣，不能讓她見你
Okay, okay.
好，好，好！我躲起來
-What? -I forgot my bat.
-怎麼了？ -忘了拿球棒
Oh, my God.
天！
And for the last time, we do not want to be friends with you!
最後警告，我們不想和你做朋友！
And we don't wanna buy your bat!
也不想買你的球棒！
What are you doing here?
你在這兒幹什麼？
Bert. Bert. Bert. Bert.
-Are you friends with him? -I can explain.
-你們是朋友？ -我來解釋
Joey?
喬伊你說
All right. Okay.
好吧！
You have got some nerve coming back here.
你還敢回來
-I can't believe you never called me. -Excuse me?
-你竟不打電話給我 -啊？
You probably don't even remember my name. It's Joey, by the way.
你連我名字也忘了，我叫喬伊
And don't bother telling me yours, because I totally remember it, lady.
不必說你的名字，我記得，女士
I waited weeks for you to call me.
我一直等你電話
I gave you my number. You never called me.
我給你電話號碼，你沒聯絡我
Don't try to turn this around on me.
還想栽贓給我
I am not some kind of social work..
我可不是讓你
that you can just..
為所欲為的
do.
〞社工〞
-I'm pretty sure I gave you my number. -Really? Think about it. Come on.
-我確信給過你電話 -真的？你想想看
You're a beautiful woman. Smart, funny.
你漂亮，聰明，有趣
We had a really good time.
咱們春風一度
If I had your number, why wouldn't I call you?
如果我有你電話，怎麼可能不打給你？
I don't know.
我就是不知道呀
Well, maybe I'm wrong. I'm sorry.
可能我搞錯了，對不起
Hey, too late for apologies. Okay? You broke my heart.
現在道歉太晚啦 你傷了我的心
You know how many women I had to sleep with to get over you?
就為了忘掉你，我睡了多少女人啊！
-Joey, wait.. -No!
-喬伊，等等 -不！
I waited a long time! I can't wait anymore.
我等得夠久，不可能再等了
I'm sorry that you had to see that. I'm so embarrassed.
抱歉讓你們笑話了，真尷尬
-Oh, that's really okay. -Yeah. We totally understand.
-沒事， -我們理解
-Dating is hard. -Boy, you people are nice.
-約會可夠人受的 -你們真是好人
And I've got to say..
我得說…
I think you're going to make excellent parents.
你們一定會是很棒的父母
Laura!
勞拉！
We're back.
我們回來啦
Are you here to take more money?
還想要錢
Because I think what you're looking for is an ATM.
你們應該找提款機
No, no, we're here to give the money back.
不不, 我們把錢退給你們
Yeah. Because you know what? It's all about the children.
為了孩子
Although it's also about the wedding.
至於我們的婚禮
All right, here. No. Oh, God.
好吧, 給.不要!喔天啊!
If I haven't said so already, sir, congratulations.
好像忘了道喜，恭喜你們
Oh, wait. Wait.
哦, 等等
What if we give half to the charity and we keep half?
如果我們捐一半留一半呢?
Or, no, like,75 percent for us and 25 percent for.. Or, no, like,90-10.
或者, 就像我們留75%, 而另外25%... 或者, 就像9--1分帳....
Okay, you know what? Enough, all right?
好啦!你知道嗎?已經夠了, 好嗎?
I'm stepping in and putting my foot down.
我要插手, 而且做決定
As your future husband, I'm gonna make this decision for us.
作為你的 未來老公，我要說了算
What do you think we should do?
你說咋辦？
-It's not your decision anymore. -What?
-不是你們說了算了 -什麼？
On behalf of the children of New York, I reject your money.
代表紐約兒童，我拒收你們的捐款
-But we're giving you this. -And I'm giving it back to you.
-但是我們在給你錢啊 -退給你們
Come on. Consider it a contribution.
當作禮金好了
Well, this is very generous.
你真大方
Take the check. Have a great wedding and a wonderful life together.
支票拿走，祝婚禮成功，幸福甜蜜
Sounds good to me. We can save up, come back in a few years..
聽來不錯，我們以後存了錢
and make an even bigger donation.
過兩年捐更多
And when you do, ask for Brian.
好得很，下次記得找布萊恩捐
-Oh, is that you? -No.
-布萊恩是你? -不！
Hello?
喂？
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨！
Oh, my God, really? I can't wait to tell Chandler.
喂，天啊，真的，等不及要告訴錢德
Okay. Goodbye.
好，再見！
-Wrong number? -That was Laura.
－打錯電話的？ －是勞拉
She gave us a great report and we're officially on the waiting list.
她替我們大大美言 我們正式上了領養排隊名單
-That's great. -Now we just wait for a call..
－太好了！ －下個電話
and someone tells us there's a baby waiting for us.
就會有人說有BB等我們去領養了
Hello?
喂?
Have you seen Joey's bat?
看見喬伊的球棒嗎？
Okay. I got a spider.
好了， 我捉到了蜘蛛！
There were two, I picked the bigger one.
有兩隻，我挑了大的一隻。
-Okay. -Okay.
-好的 -好的
This feels perfectly normal.
感覺一切正常。
Okay, get on the swing.
好了，你上鞦韆去
Okay.
好啊
好
Okay.
好啊！
-See? -All right. I can do this.
-看到了嗎? -啊，沒事了，我可以玩鞦韆了。
There you go. Good for you.
是啊。幹得好！
You know what? I'm getting used to this little guy.
知道嗎？ 我習慣小蜘蛛啦。
-I don't even feel him in here anymore. -That's because he's on your neck.
-完全沒有異樣的感覺。 -因為它爬上你脖子啦